我等不及想要去看侏罗纪公园了
还有速度与激情
我超喜欢范·迪塞尔
请问一下
Excuse me?
我们这里离环球影业近吗
We are close to Universal Studios?
那儿离这儿十英里远呢
It's about ten miles away.
哦
Oh.
电脑上说这家旅馆离所有景点是最近的
太安静了 感觉像墓穴一样
我不喜欢这里
你第一次按铃我就听见了
I heard you the first time.
预定了吗
Reservations?
都怪我们
我们提前付了房费但我们不能住在这儿
这里离我们想去的地方有点远
你们的旅馆对我们来说不太合适
For us, uh, your hotel is not right.
你可以把订金还给我们吗
You will please give us back our deposit?
不能退款
No refunds.
但我们需要这笔钱去找另一家旅馆
But we need the money for a new hotel.
欢迎来到美利坚
Welcome to America.
我们应该怎么办
这家旅馆是复古风
也许会很有趣
你们已经预付了一晚房费
Look, you've already paid for one night.
相信我
Trust me.
你们会爱上这个地方的
This place will grow on you.
我忘了问您无线网密码是多少了
Um, I-I forgot to ask you the password for Wi-Fi.
我们没有那种东西
We don't have that.
事实上 整栋大楼都没有手机信号
In fact, this whole building is a dead zone for cell service.
为了方便起见每个房间里有一部电话
There is a telephone in each room for your convenience.
本地通话免费
Local calls are free.
弄丢房门钥匙要赔偿五十美金
$50 fee for losing your keys.
还有什么需要我帮忙的吗
Anything else I can help you with?
有冰块吗
Ice?
制冰机在左边第二个走廊
Ice machine is down the second hallway to the left.
请自便
Knock yourself out.
51号房发生了可怕的意外 太吓人了
Terrible accident in room 51; just ghastly!
你闻到了吗
房间里有股怪味
像动物的尸臭味
我把所有蜡烛都用上了还是很臭
前台
Front desk.
我们要换房
We must change rooms.
这间房里有股难闻的味道
There's a terrible smell in here.
我们旅馆是有点发霉
It's a musty hotel.
试试把空调风力开大一点
Try running the air conditioner on high.
不行 你必须给我们换一间房
No, you must give us another room!
房间都被订完了
We're sold out.
没有空房
Nothing available.
那个贱人
那股怪味
来自这里
别这么做 维德拉
弄坏了我们还要赔钱
我才不在乎
官网：www.sskzmz.com
DARREN
LUKE
BUNNY  MARK
HHJIE
Luv_DC
美国恐怖故事
旅馆
那人是谁 那是什么东西
Who was that?! What was that?
我不知道啊
I have no idea.
亲爱的 我和你们一样害怕
Honey, I'm just as upset as you are.
我想让你们知道
And I want you to know
你们不用付那间房的房费了
you will not be charged for that room.
这鬼地方我一秒钟也待不下去了
I cannot stay in this place one more second!
警察一会就会过来
The police will be coming soon.
要么你们在这儿录口供
You can either give them a statement here
要么一会儿你们因为躲避警察
or you can talk to them later in jail
被抓到监狱里去和他们说
when they arrest you for evasion.
我去把你的行李拿过来
I'll get your bags ready.
在那之前
Until then,
你们可以待在这儿
you can stay here.
你不是说没有空房了吗
I thought you said it was no other room.
这间房我们从来都不租出去
This one we never rent out.
一 小 时 后
很抱歉
We're sorry.
拨号失败
Your call cannot be completed as dialed.
请核对后再拨
Please check the number and dial again.
没有信号
我就知道
我要在尖叫点评上给这家旅馆写差评
阿吉
Aggie?
所以我们认为犯罪嫌疑人从管家手里偷来钥匙
So, we think our guy lifted the master key from housekeeping.
有人听到什么吗
Nobody heard anything?
看起来两位受害者一走进房门
Looks like both victims were chloroformed
就被氯仿麻醉了
the second they walked through the door.
有趣
Lovely.
让屋里亮起来
Let's get some light in here.
男性受害者的眼球在烟灰缸里
Male victim's eyeballs are in the ashtray.
还有他的舌头
And his tongue?
他现在生不如死
He's in a world of hurt.
放我
Get me...
约翰 这片区域已经记录过了
John, this area's been documented already.
我还没看过
Not by me.
他们都是已婚 不过和对方不是夫妻关系
They were married, but not to each other.
他们当时在偷情
They were cheating.
也许被惹怒的配偶作案
Very pissed-off spouse, maybe.
不 这不是情杀
No, this isn't jealousy.
肯定有别的动机
This is something else.
凶手要表达的意思是
The killer's saying the families
他们的家人被蒙在鼓里
are blind to what's been going on.
放我出去
Get me out...
先生
Sir?
我们会放你出去的
We're gonna get you out of here.
我保证
We promise.
他不是这么说的
That's not what he's saying.
他说的是 让我从她里面出来
He's saying, "Get me out of her."
他还在她身体里
He's still inside of her.
你会在他体内
You're gonna find
发现壮阳药 或许有很多
male potency drugs in his system; probably a lot.
你现在没办法把他们分开
You won't be able to detach them here,
所以你不得不把尸体和他一并带走
so you're gonna have to take him with the corpse.
给他松开
Cut him loose.
你帮我拿到报告了吗
You have that report for me?
法医还在现场调查
Forensics is still on the scene.
不 我说的不是今早的杀人案
No, not from the homicide this morning.
我说的是上个月的马丁·甘博阿的案子
From the Martin Gamboa case, last month.
受害者叫 马丁·甘博阿
The victim's name-- Martin Gamboa,
四十七岁
age 47.
职业为奥斯卡博客作家
Profession listed as Oscar blogger.
187号案子发生在位于银湖区的死者家中
187 occurred in victim's home in Silver Lake.
受害者死于头部钝器重击
Victim died from blunt force trauma to the head.
手臂和胸部也有伤口
There's evidence of wounds on arms
有些是防卫所致
and thorax; some defensive.
凶手一开始想要折磨他
Whoever did this wanted him to suffer first.
右臂的桡骨和尺骨骨折
Fractures to the radius and the ulna of the right arm;
右臂肱骨开放性骨折
compound fractures of the humerus of the left arm
骨头穿过皮肤突出来
with bone protrusions through the skin.
在直肠腔和头盖骨里
There are traces of what appear to be gold paint chips
貌似有一些金漆碎片残留
in the rectal cavity as well as in what is left of the cranium,
未发现凶器
所以可以猜测不管凶器是什么
so it may be assumed that whatever the murder weapon was,
它还被用作性侵犯
was also used in the sexual assault...
嗨 爸爸
Hi, Dad!
学校怎么样
How was school?
很好 莉兹·库珀在拼写时
Good. Lizzy Cooper threw up
紧张到呕吐
in the middle of spelling.
虽然挺恶心的 但也很有趣
It was gross and awesome at the same time.
男孩们现在都叫他莉兹·呕吐怪了
The boys are calling her Lizzy Puker now.
妈妈呢 她想和我说几句吗
How's Mom? Does she want to talk to me?
嘿 妈妈 你要和爸爸打个招呼吗
Hey, Mom, do you want to say hi to Dad?
不了 亲爱的
No, honey.
你吃饭了吗
Did you eat?
吃了 骗子
Yes. Liar.
好啦 你准备好讲故事了吗 快到睡觉时间了
All right, you ready to read? It's almost bedtime.
洛
Lowe?
三号线上有你的电话
You got a call on line three.
帮我留言
Take a message.
他很执着
Uh, he was pretty adamant.
我也是
So am I.
老爸 你去忙吧
Daddy, you can go.
不行
Nope.
我们要讲睡前故事
We read at bedtime.
谁先来
Who's gonna start?
你
You.
好吧
All right.
男孩们已经耗尽了所有耐心 天知道
"Boys are trying enough to human patience, goodness knows,
但女孩们绝对更为...”
"But girls are infinitely more so..."
你能前后对照一下甘博阿和
Can you cross-reference the Gamboa forensics
旅馆案件的取证吗 比如指纹什么的
with the hotel case-- prints, everything?
没问题
You got it.
你好
Hello?
你好 约翰
Hello, John.
你为什么不接我的电话
Why didn't you take my call?
你是谁
Who is this?
你怎么会有我的号码
How'd you get this number?
我把他们钉到床头板上了
I nailed them to the headboard.
我在科尔特兹旅馆的64号房
I'm at the Hotel Cortez, room 64.
我将会旧戏重演
I'm going to do it again.
我要一间房 就住一晚
I need a room, one night.
一百五十美元
150.
这里说是三十美元 这个是以前的价格
It says here 30.  It's out of date.
重新装修后涨价了
Prices went up after the remodel.
你在扯淡吧
Okay, well, that's bullshit.
你知道吗
You know what?
今天算你走运
It's your lucky day.
老娘今天宽宏大量
Mama's feeling magnanimous.
64号房
Room 64.
噢 电梯今天不能用了
Oh, elevator's out of service today.
这个我先要了 艾丽斯
I got dibs on this one, Iris.
好久没见过这样的鲜肉了
I haven't seen one that sweet in a while.
人一死 就会弄脏床单
When people die, they soil the sheets--
血啊 屎啊 尿啊
blood, shit, urine.
任何污渍我都能清理干净
I can take care of every stain there is.
哇呜
Woof.
你可真养眼呀
You're a sight for sore eyes,
警官先生
Mr. Police Officer.
有这么明显吗 嗯哼
-It's that obvious, huh? -Mm-hmm.
你肯定经常和警察打交道吧
You must have a lot of run-ins with police.
还行吧
My fair share.
你能告诉我64号房住客的情况么
What can you tell me about the occupant in room 64?
那间房是空的
That room's vacant.
你介意我上去看一眼么
You mind if I take a quick look?
悉听尊便
Oh, be my guest.
丽兹·泰勒
Liz Taylor.
带这位好警官去64号房
Show this nice policeman to room 64.
64号 是的
64? Yes.
64号房
Room 64.
马上去
Right away.
救我
Help me!
救救我
你叫得越大声 他就越喜欢
The more you scream, the more he likes it.
你能和我说说在这旅馆出入的
What can you tell me about the people
都是哪些人吗
that come in and out of this place?
大多是长期住客还是暂时住客
They mostly residents or transients?
噢 这儿什么人都有
Oh, we got a bit of everything.
有的开包月房 有的开钟点房
Some pay by the month, some pay by the hour.
有些老前辈很久以前就住在这了
Some of the old-timers have been here since the dawn of time.
那你呢
And you?
你要找什么
Who are you looking for?
无可奉告
Not at liberty to say.
噢 我不是那个意思
Oh, I don't mean that.
我能看到你眼神里的悲痛
I can see the pain in your eyes.
似曾相识的眼神
It's very familiar.
噢 你失去了什么东西
Oh, you've lost something.
如今你卡在了时间里
And now you're frozen in time.
停滞不前了
Can't move forward.
也不能回头
Can't go back.
说你爱我
Tell me you love me.
说出来
Say it!
说“我爱你 莎莉” 它就会消失了
Say, "I love you, Sally," And it will all go away.
说啊
Say it.
我爱你 莎莉
I love you, Sally.
再说一遍
Say it again.
再说 一遍
Say it... again.
我爱你 萨利
I love you, Sally.
好了 我自己进去就行了
Alright, I'll take it from here.
我没带现金
I don't have any cash.
金钱不是万能的
Money isn't everything.
霍顿
Holden?
我们现在为什么不做爱呢
#有个大计划 他决定了 或许是对的#
# Got a big plan, his mind's set, maybe it's right #
#正确的时间 正确的地点 或许就今晚#
# At the right place and right time, maybe tonight #
#一次私语 一次握手 传达了讯息#
# In a whisper or handshake, sending the sign #
#想要亲热 用力拥吻 等等  别管了#
# Want to make out and kiss hard; wait, never mind #
#夜深随口提及了它#
# Late night in passing mention it #
#最好的朋友 又算什么呢 或许这次失手了#
# Flip to her best friend, it's no thing, maybe it slipped #
#但过失会变成恐慌以及迷恋的心跳#
# But the slip turns to terror and a crush to like #
更多欧美音乐资讯
关注微博：Luv_DC
#她走进来 他呆住了 只剩下害怕#
# And she walked, he froze up, leave it to fright #
#有点可爱 以至你无法言语#
# It's cute in a way till you cannot speak #
#而你却离开抽烟 双膝发软#
# And you leave to have a cigarette, knees get weak #
#只是一时心动 会过去的#
# It's only just a crush, it'll go away #
#就像其他的感觉一样 会过去的#
# It's just like all the others, it'll go away #
#或者这很危险 而你尚未察觉#
# Or maybe this is danger, and you just don't know #
#你祈祷想要摆脱 感觉却愈演愈烈#
# You pray it all away, but it continues to grow #
#啊 我想要紧紧拥你入怀#
# Ah... # # I want to hold you close #
#我们肌肤相贴#
# Skin pressed against me tight #
#躺着不动 闭上眼吧 宝贝女孩#
# Lie still, close your eyes, girl #
#如此可爱 感觉如此美好#
# So lovely, it feels so right #
#我想紧紧拥你入怀#
# I want to hold you close #
#柔软的呼吸 跳动的心房#
# Soft breath, beating heart #
#当我在你耳边低语#
# As I whisper in your ear #
#我想将你身体撕裂#
# "I want to tear you apart" #
#然后他走进来告诉她#
# Then he walked up and told her #
#想着或许这感觉会过去的#
# Thinking maybe it'd pass #
#他们交谈 看向别处 开始跳舞#
# And they talked and looked away a lot, doing the dance #
#她的手和他的相碰 她没有回避#
# Her hand brushed up against his, she left it there #
#告诉他她的感受 他们相互凝视#
# Told him how she felt, and then they locked in a stare #
#他们后退了一步 仔细考虑 他们该怎么办#
# They took a step back, thought about it, what should they do? #
#因为在学校约会#
# 'Cause there's always repercussions #
#总会有些影响#
# When you're dating in school #
#但他们的双唇相碰 那些迟疑早已抛下#
# But their lips met, and reservations started to pass #
#不管只有今晚#
# Whether this was just an evening #
#或还有后续#
# Or a thing that would last #
#无论怎样 都很糟糕#
# Either way he wanted her, and this was bad #
#想对她做的事 让他抓狂#
# Wanted to do things to her, it was making him crazy #
#现在一点心动变成了喜欢#
# Now a little crush turned into a like #
#现在他想抓着她的头发告诉她#
# And now he wants to grab her by the hair and tell her #
#啊 我想紧紧拥你入怀#
# Ah... # # I want to hold you close #
#我们肌肤相贴#
# Skin pressed against me tight #
#躺着不动 闭上眼吧 宝贝女孩#
# Lie still, close your eyes, girl #
#如此可爱 感觉如此美好#
# So lovely, it feels so right #
#我想紧紧拥你入怀#
# I want to hold you close #
#柔软的呼吸 跳动的心房#
# Soft breath, beating heart #
#当我在你耳边低语#
# As I whisper in your ear #
#我想将你身体撕裂#
# "I want to tear you apart" #
#我想紧紧拥你入怀#
# I want to hold you close #
#我们肌肤相贴#
# Skin pressed against me tight #
#躺着不动 闭上眼吧 宝贝女孩#
# Lie still, close your eyes, girl #
#如此可爱 感觉如此美好#
# So lovely, it feels so right #
#我想紧紧拥你入怀#
# I want to hold you close #
#柔软的呼吸 跳动的心房#
# Soft breath, beating heart #
#当我在你耳边低语#
# As I whisper in your ear #
#我想将你身体撕裂#
# "I want to tear you apart" #
#我想紧紧拥你入怀#
# I want to hold you close #
#我们肌肤相贴#
# Skin pressed against me tight #
#躺着不动 闭上眼吧 宝贝女孩#
# Lie still, close your eyes, girl #
#如此可爱 感觉如此美好#
# So lovely, it feels so right #
#我想紧紧拥你入怀#
# I want to hold you close #
#柔软的呼吸 跳动的心房#
# Soft breath, beating heart #
#当我在你耳边低语#
# As I whisper in your ear #
#我想将你身体撕裂#
# "I want to tear you apart" #
#我想紧紧拥你入怀#
# I want to hold you close #
#柔软的呼吸 跳动的心房#
# Soft breath, beating heart #
#当我在你耳边低语#
# As I whisper in your ear #
#我想将你身体撕裂#
# "I want to tear you apart." #
你还说今晚不想出门
And you didn't feel like going out tonight.
不是懒得准备
It's not the getting ready,
是打扫太麻烦
it's the clean up.
快叫清洁工
Call housekeeping.
爹地
Daddy!
嘿
Hey.
我一直在等这个大拥抱
That's what I've been looking for.
你怎么样啦
How you doing?
很好啊 你呢
Good, how are you?
嘿 很抱歉迟到了
Hey, sorry I'm late.
你收到我的短信了吗
Did you get my text?
收到了 它比你体贴多了
Yes, and it's clearly more considerate than you,
因为收到短信的时间就是你该出现的时间
'cause it showed up at 6:00 like you were supposed to.
抱歉
Sorry.
有个贝弗利山庄的孩子崴到了脚踝
Have a kid with a sprained ankle in Beverly Hills
祸不单行的是又有一对帕利塞兹的
and twins with possible whooping cough
双胞胎奇怪地咳嗽
in the Palisades right after.
奇怪地咳嗽
Whooping cough.
你也不相信对吧 让我去帮帮妈妈
Can you believe it? Let me help your mother.
这些人也不知道怎么回事
What's wrong with people?
我不在乎他们付我多少钱
I don't care how much they pay me,
我就是看不爽这些父母到处夸张他们孩子的病情
I refuse to see parents who won't "Vax" Their kids.
医生
Doctor.
我做了你们俩都喜欢的藜麦砂锅
I made that quinoa casserole you two like.
噢 那太棒了
Oh, good.
你还好吗
You okay?
还好了
Yeah, yeah.
我只是有点饿了
I'm just hungry, I think.
好吧 下次你应该吃点
Well, next time you should eat
我塞在你口袋里的蛋白棒
the protein bar I stuffed in your pocket.
爱你哟 拜 妈妈
Love you. Bye, Mom.
爱你
Love you.
寿司
Sushi?
你怎么知道
Read my mind.
我是谁啊
Yeah.
求你了 让我们走吧
Please, let us go.
啊 省点力气吧
Eh, stop your whining.
这是你们自找的
You brought this on yourselves.
我也经历过这事儿
I went through your shit.
看起来你们俩是计划着一场欲仙欲死的派对啊
Looks like the two of you were planning quite the party.
阿普唑仓 氯硝西泮制剂[抗抑郁惊厥药物]
Xanax. Klonopin.
我可不管这些粉红色的小药片到底是什么
Whatever the hell those pink pills were.
那是治疗失眠的药
Those are for sleeping.
你们妈妈知道你们是一对不知廉耻的瘾君子吗
Your mothers know you're a couple of shameless junkies?
你们的身体被这些毒品玷污了
You're polluting your bodies with all that shit.
愚蠢的瑞典笨蛋
You dumb Swedish meatballs.
但是我们会好好帮你们净化的
We're gonna fix that right up.
没错 我们要涤净你们整个消化系统
Yeah, we're gonna flush your system,
把你们带回健康的状态
bring you back to the epitome of health.
来看看我们今天为你们准备了什么
Just look at the spread we got for you today.
牡蛎
Oysters.
富含锌和维生素B12
Full of zinc and B12.
提高免疫力的哦
Boost your immunity,
让你们的伤口好得更快
help your wounds heal faster.
还有一点鸡肝
And we got you some chicken livers...
肾 富含铁哦
...kidneys, packed with iron.
要让你们的红细胞活跃起来
Get those red blood cells pumping.
压轴戏来了
And to top it off,
再加点教皇新堡葡萄酒
a Chateauneuf-du-Pape Grenache blanc.
没错
Yeah.
拜托 拜托 不要 唔
Please. Please, don't. Mmm.
闭嘴
Shut up.
这只是帮助你们身体
This is just the thing to get your bodies
吸收这些营养的好东西而已
to absorb all these nutrients.
不要 不要 不要
Stop. Stop. Stop.
拜托你 不要这样
Don't. Please don't...
你们可以自己吃 也可以等我灌你们吃
We can do this the easy way or the hard way.
但我是不会离开的哦
But I'm not leaving
直到你们把所有维他命和矿物质都吃完
until you get all your vitamins and minerals.
求求你 求求你
Please, please.
好了 来吧
All right. Come on.
不 不 不 谁最爱吃营养早餐啊
No! No! No! Breakfast of champions.
张开嘴
Open your mouth.
你一定要这么残忍吗
Do you really need to be so aggressive?
你就不能有点怜悯之心吗
Can't you have some compassion?
你给我滚出去
You get the hell out of here.
你从来不顾这些女孩死活的 那你就在乎吗
You don't give a shit about these girls. And you do?
我知道你的关心是什么
I've seen what your caring looks like.
我们大家心知肚明
We've all seen it.
至少我有关心的人和事
At least I care about something.
你以为我想在这里吗 周围都是瘾君子和腐朽的东西
Think I want to be here, surrounded by junkies and decay?
好吧 那你为什么不离开呢 走啊
Well, then why don't you leave? Go.
你这二十年来一直在抱怨同一件事
You've been whining about the same thing for 20 years.
你不停地逼逼啊逼逼
You talk a good talk,
但是你从没离开过 因为事实就是你爱死这里了
but you stick around because the truth is you like it.
不是的
No.
让我困在这个肮脏的
I'm stuck in this godforsaken cesspool
充满痛苦的沼泽的罪魁祸首就是你
of pain and shit 'cause of you.
额
Eh.
你就是我痛苦的根源
You're the beginning and the end
和结尾
of all my suffering.
很好
Good.
我受够了
Well, I'm done.
受够了这个烂摊子
Done with your bullshit.
受够这里了
Done with it all.
你以为你自己比我做得好吗
You think you can do this better?
那你自己来吧
Then you do it yourself.
但你最好能把这工作做好
But you better do a good job.
不然你自己去跟她解释 为什么她们还是这种味道
Otherwise you can explain to her why they still taste like shit.
我去喂33号房的那个东西了
I got to go feed that thing in room 33.
求你了
Please.
你们知道这间房子以前是干什么的吗
Do you know what this room used to be?
是用来演木偶戏的
This old dude used to put on a puppet show right there.
提线木偶人 用线穿着 供大家消遣娱乐
Marionettes, strings, for entertainment.
而你们现在呢
And now you...
要来供我消遣娱乐了
...are going to entertain me.
用你们的眼泪感动我吧
Move me with your tears.
跑吧
Run.
跑啊
Run!
维德拉 别丢下我
别把我扔在这儿啊
哦 糟了
Oh, crap.
我不知道怎么回事
I don't know what happened.
她不知怎的逃了出来
She got loose somehow.
这种事情不允许再发生
This can never happen again.
我们该问问这些是不是日本的鱼肉
Shouldn't we ask if any of this fish is from Japan?
为什么
Why?
有辐射啊
Radiation.
你真像你的妈妈
You're starting to sound like your mother.
她总说小心一点是没错的
She always said she had a good reason to worry.
我昨晚又梦到他了
I had a dream about him again last night.
我没办法再看清他的脸了
I can't see his face anymore.
我只有在梦里才能想起那张脸
I can't remember it except in my dreams,
那样我才能看见
then I can really see it.
但是我一醒来
When I wake up...
我就记不清了
I can't remember.
你醒来后还记得他的样子吗
Do you remember what he looks like when you're awake?
是
Yeah.
也许我们应该把照片重新挂出来
Maybe we should put the pictures up again.
饭桌上不要玩手机
No electronics at the dinner table.
是你的妈妈
It's your mom.
我在深谷路432号
快来救我
这里是亚利克斯 请留言
You've reached Alex, please leave a message.
爸爸 怎么了 进去看了吗
Dad, what's happening?! Been inside yet?
没有 我才到 怎么了 警探
No, I just got here. What's going on, Detective?
还不知道 看着我女儿
I don't know yet. Watch my daughter.
亚历克斯 你还好吗
Alex, are you okay?
约翰·洛
John Lowe.
你是谁
Who is this?
我妻子呢
Where's my wife?!
我说过我会再干一次
I told you I'd do it again.
把手举起来
Show me your hands!
站住
Stop...
Stop!
斯嘉丽
Scarlett!
好了 亲爱的 你瞄准了吗
All right, honey, you got it?
哇 差一点
Oh, so close.
我带霍顿去坐旋转木马
I'm gonna take Holden to the carousel.
好的 宝贝
All right, babe.
走吧 伙计
Come on, buddy.
慢点来 慢点来
Slow it down, slow it down.
记住像拿铅笔一样握住
Remember, hold it like a pencil.
然后像扔棒球一样扔出去
Throw it like a baseball.
瞄准目标
Concentrate on where you want it to go.
好了吗 开始
Ready? Go.
哇 你真棒
Oh! Good job!
圣塔莫尼卡 2010年
你饿了吗 伙计
You hungry, buddy?
嗯 我想吃棉花糖
Yeah, I want some cotton candy.
饿了要吃正餐的啊
You got to eat some real food first.
我还没有那么饿
I'm not hungry for that.
是吗 那骑完之后再去吃东西
No? All right, we'll get something after.
好了
Here you go.
这个马脚是黄色的
You got one with yellow feet.
很特别哟
He's a special one.
霍顿
Holden?
你看见我儿子了吗
Hey, you seen my boy?
他坐在黄脚的木马上
He was on that horse with the yellow feet.
霍顿
Holden!
Holden?!
霍顿
Holden!
霍顿 霍顿
Holden! Holden!
也许我们该搬到玛丽那里去
I mean, maybe we should just go stay with Mary.
新罕布什尔州吗 我不想这样对斯嘉丽
In New Hampshire? I don't want to do that to Scarlett.
她已经很难受了
It's already gonna be hard enough as it is.
她应该在自己的床上睡觉
She should be able to sleep in her own bed.
我会安排两名警察时刻跟着你们
I'm gonna have two uniformed men with you at all times.
一个跟着斯嘉丽去上学
One's gonna go to school with Scarlett, one's gonna go
一个跟着你上班 他们都很优秀
to work with you, and these guys are very good at what they do.
你不会意识到他们跟着你的 一旦你需要帮助 他们就会出现
You're not even gonna know they are there unless you need them.
你知道这个人的样子吗
Do you even know what this guy looks like?
我不知道他怎么用我的手机给你发了短信
I don't understand how he texted you from my phone.
你觉得他知道我们住在哪里吗
I mean, do you think that he knows where we live?
天呐 约翰
Jesus, John.
我们该怎么办
What are we gonna do, huh?
也许我该买把枪
Maybe I should get a gun.
不 你不需要买枪 好吗
No. No, you-you don't need to get a gun, all right?
他肯定有复制手机的办法
There are ways to clone somebody's phone, all right?
不要担心
Don't worry.
我会保护你们的安全
I'm gonna keep you guys safe.
怎么保护 搬出去吗
What, by moving out?
我感觉他还会来找我
I have a feeling he's gonna come after me again,
如果是这样的话 我不想让你们在我身边
and if that happens, I don't want either of you near me.
听着 我不是因为你要走而伤心
Look, I'm not upset because you're leaving.
而是因为
I'm upset because I...
我想过让你离开
I secretly want you to go.
我理解
I-I understand. You...
我不该把斯嘉丽带到那个房子
I shouldn't have brought Scarlett to that house.
我以为你遇到了麻烦
I thought you were in trouble,
我叫那个白痴警察看着她
I-I told that idiot cop to watch her.
我不是因为那个生气
I'm not mad about that.
我知道你不会让她受到伤害
I know you would never put her in danger.
霍顿的事情 我也不怪你
And I don't blame you for Holden.
不管你是怎么想的
No matter what you think.
我很爱你
I love you so much.
他和你长得太像了
He looks just so much like you.
我每天看着你 就像看到了他
I see him in your face
我恨不得去死
every day and I just want to die.
这不公平 他们抢走了我的儿子
It's not fair-- they took my little boy from me,
我却甚至不能正眼看着
and I can't even look at the one person in the world
这世上唯一了解我感受的人
who understands how I feel.
我只是需要远离这一切
I just need a break from it all.
你有过希望吗
Do you ever hope?
我一直都在希望着
I can't stop hoping.
那才是最难受的
That's the worst part.
科尔特兹酒店
欢迎
Welcome.
雨停了
The rain may have stopped,
但今天还是阴天
but it's still a gloomy day.
我不得不把我的狗送去安乐死
I had to put my dog down.
他在不幸的处境时找上了我
He came to me through very unfortunate circumstances.
但你们不会想听的
But you don't need to hear about that.
这边走
Right this way.
这里的建筑物都是历史遗迹
So many buildings around here are time capsules,
由非个人的企业信托所保管
locked away by an impersonal business trust.
我喜欢和信托打交道
I prefer dealing with a trust.
匿名而且实事求是
Anonymous. Unsentimental.
你是来这里住 还是来这里工作
So you'll live here, or just work here?
我知道你对顶楼很感兴趣
I know that you were interested in the top floor.
我们全搬过来了
We're moving our life out here.
我无法区分工作与家庭
Work, home-- I've never kept them separate.
对我来说很明确 洛杉矶曾是艺术的天堂
It's very clear to me: the art world has looked to L.A.,
潮流会紧随而来
and fashion is soon to follow.
我会住在顶楼
The top floor is where I'll live
下面就是现成的工作室
and just below will be an atelier, mostly ready-to-wear.
拉克伦
Lachlan!
Lachlan?
噢
Oh.
他真是活泼
So much energy.
有什么需要帮忙的吗
How can I help you?
额 我是卖房子的地产经纪人
Uh, I'm the realtor
我来带他们看房子
representing the sale. We're here for the walk-through.
我们有需要会告诉你的
We'll let you know if we need anything.
卖房子
Sale?
什么卖房子
What sale?
我知道
Well, I know it was
这件事还没公开
a whisper listing, but surely,
但房主肯定告诉了你吧
the owner should have told you.
没人他妈的告诉我
Nobody tells me shit.
我连房主都没见过
I've never even met the owner.
那你现在见到了 亲爱的
Well, you have now, dearie.
这是新房主威尔·德雷克先生
This is the new owner, Mr. Will Drake.
我们先看顶层的套房吧
We'll start with the penthouse?
有需要会告诉你的
We'll let you know if we need anything.
我们要去睡大街了
We're gonna be turned out onto the streets.
云已经散开了
The clouds have cleared.
可以一直看到太平洋
Sightlines all the way to the Pacific.
拉上窗帘
Close it!
光太亮了
The light!
你们他妈的是谁
Who the hell are you people?
你们在我房间里干什么
And what are you doing in my room?
我们被侵入了
We've been invaded.
被卖了
Shanghaied!
一个该死的纽约客在我的套房里面量尺寸
Some goddamn New Yorker is sizing up my suite.
这个点儿对你来说有点早了 不是吗
A little early for you, isn't it?
我知道你会更喜欢
I know you'll prefer the view
我们刚才见到的景
from the space we just saw,
但这里是这层楼的另外一半
but here's the other half of the floor plan.
当然了 光照问题是个挑战
The lighting is, of course, a challenge
但我不知道这些霓虹灯能不能起点作用
and I don't know if all this neon is the answer.
威尔·德雷克
Will Drake.
见到你真荣幸
I am so pleased to meet you.
你为奥巴马夫人做的那套礼服
I was completely impressed with the gown you made
真的让我印象深刻
for Mrs. Obama.
那是宴请
It was the state dinner for...
西班牙领导人的国宴 没错
The Spaniards, yes.
听你提起倍感荣幸
Kind of you to mention.
我在食疗净化
I'm on a cleanse.
从现在开始不是了
Not anymore.
拉克兰 说你呢
Lachlan! Honestly.
指纹是最不容易擦掉的
Fingerprints are really hard to get off.
无心之过都是可以原谅的
Messes are always forgiven.
第一次的时候
The first time.
-那是 -没错
Is... Yes.
这是艾力克·李维的作品
It's an Arik Levy
是我自己的藏品
and it doesn't come with the building.
当然了 我更希望你能像我们一样
Of course, I'm hopeful you're as interested
对科尔特兹本身感兴趣
in the character of The Cortez as we are.
这里充满了能量
There's energy here.
我走过无数纽约街道
I walk through New York
而我再也没有听见过音乐声
streets and I don't hear the music anymore.
再也没有能与我产生共鸣的东西
No more echos of who I was there.
街道被重建 历史的痕迹被抹掉
Blocks are toppled, history erased,
到处都是怪人
weirdoes banished.
这里简直就是另外一个世界
This place is far enough away
能与我交流
that it speaks to me--
甚至在对我歌唱
it sings, even.
我已经等不及
Well, I cannot wait
要看看你能把这里改造成什么样子
to see what you make of it.
说得真动听
That's really beautiful.
那像我们这样的怪人
So where are weirdoes like us
该住在哪儿呢
supposed to live, huh?
有没有哪首歌告诉你这件事
Any songs telling you anything about that?
或许你可以为我们的邻居
Perhaps you could show our neighbor
展示一下詹姆斯·特瑞尔的光雕
the James Turrell light sculpture?
爸爸 我能留下来看看这些唱片吗
Dad, can I stay and look at the records?
当然可以了
Of course you can.
人们不该住在旅馆里
People aren't supposed to live in hotels.
或许这里是特例
Well, maybe this place is special.
我带你去一些看你会感兴趣的东西如何
I want to show you something you'll enjoy.
一会儿就回来
We'll only be gone a moment.
我很多年前曾住在纽约
I lived in New York, many years ago.
我很喜欢在街道上漫步
I loved roaming the streets,
全神贯注地感受这座城市的脉动
devouring the pulse of the city.
让我很兴奋
Electrifying.
我怀念这种感觉
I miss it very much.
在搬走的时候
Did your father give you a choice
你爸爸有给过你选择吗
when it came time to leave?
我爸爸不让我跟陌生人说话
My dad says I'm not supposed to talk to strangers.
我们不是陌生人 拉克兰
We're not strangers, Lachlan.
我们会成为好朋友的
We're going to be great friends.
到了
Here we are.
这走廊有什么好看的
What's so special about a  hallway?
霍顿 我们有客人了
Holden, we have a guest.
你的礼貌呢 小天使
Where are your manners, angel?
你好 想一起玩吗
Hello. Want to play?
你听见了吗
Did you hear?
他们卖了这栋旅馆
They sold the hotel.
我们都会被遣散的
We'll be cast to the wind.
就当这是件好事吧 妈
Consider it a blessing, Mother.
你很久之前就该离开这儿了
You should have left this place years ago.
我在这儿工作是因为我想
I'm here because I need to see you
每天都见到你
every day.
你是时候放手了
Time for you to let go.
#当你孤单一个#
# When you're alone #
#而生活逼你独自面对#
# And life is making you lonely #
#你总有个去处#
# You can always go #
#市区#
# Downtown #
#当你忧心忡忡#
# When you've got worries #
#噪音与催促让你烦扰#
# All the noise and the hurry #
#我知道有个去处#
# Seems to help, I know #
#市区#
# Downtown #
#仔细聆听那音乐#
# Just listen to the music #
#来自城市的交通熙攘#
# Of the traffic in the city... #
你能告诉我
Can you tell me
他们住在哪间吗
what room they're in?
刚刚走进来的那对儿
The couple that just came in?
抱歉 女士
I'm sorry, lady.
这里是保密旅馆
This is a no-tell motel.
那个男孩是我儿子
That boy is my son
而那个瘾君子打算让他吸毒
and that junkie's about to give him dope.
给
Here.
哦 别这样
Oh, come on.
最近的提款机在哪里
Where's the nearest ATM?
在药店里的拐角处
At the corner drugstore,
挨着卫生巾
right next to the maxi pads.
哦 兄弟
Oh, brother.
该死
Goddamn it.
可以了
There we go.
啊
Ah...
你给我一个新针头 行吗
You're gonna give me a fresh needle, right?
我是你认识的最健康的人了
I'm the cleanest person you know.
来啦
Yeah?
你给他用了什么
What'd you give him?
多诺万
Donovan?
他不省人事了
He's out cold.
谁让你进来的 女士
Who invited you in, lady?
你到底给他用了什么
What did you give him?!
中国白粉啊
China White.
他已经去了他想要去的地方了
Which means he is just where he wants to be.
报警啊 报警干嘛呀
Call 911! No one's calling anyone.
快醒醒 我告诉过他让他悠着点别学我的
Come on... I told him not to try and keep up with me.
我们用量一样
We took the same shit
而我这不还好好的
and I am more than fine.
至少在你闯进来之前我还好好的
At least until you barged in.
你不能走
You can't leave!
哦 拜托
Oh, please.
你知道我买这白粉花了多少钱吗
You know how much I paid for this dope?
哦 天啊
Oh, God.
天啊
Oh, God...
你是谁
Who are you?
你儿子的下巴我喜欢
Your boy has a jawline for days.
# On a dark desert highway #
# Cool wind in my hair #
# Warm smell of colitas #
# Rising up through the air #
# Up ahead in the distance #
# I saw a shimmering light #
# My head grew heavy and my sight grew dim #
# I had to stop for the night #
# There she stood in the doorway #
# I heard the mission bell #
# And I was thinking to myself #
# This could be heaven #
# Or this could be hell #
# Then she lit up her candle #
# And she showed me the way #
# There were voices down the corridor #
# Thought I heard them say #
# Such a lovely place #
# Such a lovely face #
# They livin' it up at the Hotel California #
# What a nice surprise #
# Bring your alibis #
# Mirrors on the ceiling #
# The pink champagne on ice #
# And she said, we are all just prisoners here #
# Of our own device #
# And in the master's chambers #
# They gathered for the feast #
# They stab it with their steely knives #
# But they just can't kill the beast #
# Last thing I remember #
# I was running for the door #
# I had to find the passage back #
# To the place I was before #
# Relax, said the night man #
# We are programmed to receive #
# You can check out any time you like #
# But you can never leave... #
下集预告